Guide to the Robert A. M. Stern Architects Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Project records for 1990-1992, 1990-2001; Accession 2016-M-0097
  - Tram, Euro Disneyland (91009), 1991
    - Project sketches (Box 123, Folder 44)
  - Residence in Beverly Park (Beverly Park, CA) (91011), 1991
    This is an unbuilt project. RAMSA ultimately built a house for same client in Montecito, CA, under RAMSA project number 93021. See Also: 93021.
    - Project file (Box 8, Folder 186-191)
    - Project images (Box 46, Folder 44)
    - Project drawings, presentation (Box 74)
    - Project sketches (Box 123, Folder 45)
  - Banana Republic on Fifth Avenue (New York, NY) (91012), 1991
    - Project images (Box 46, Folder 45)
    - Project sketches (Box 123, Folder 46)
  - Robert A.M. Stern Architects Office (New York, NY) (91013), 1991
    See Also: 85025, 90009, 92011
    - Project images (Box 46, Folder 46)
    - Project drawings (Box 74)
  - Classic Crown for Love Ball 2 (New York, NY) (91014), 1991
    - Project images (Box 46, Folder 47)
    - Project sketches, small-scale design drawings (Box 123, Folder 47)
  - America House, The United States Embassy Cultural and Consular Annex (Budapest, Hungary) (91015), 1991-1992
    See Also: 88048
    - Project file
      - Feasibility briefing and program reports (Box 9, Folder 192)
      - To client (Box 9, Folder 193-194)
      - From client (Box 9, Folder 195-196)
      - Authorities (permits, filings, and approvals) (Box 9, Folder 197)
      - Consultants (Box 9, Folder 198-199)
      - Structural (Box 9, Folder 200)
      - Mechanical (Box 9, Folder 201)
      - Electrical (Box 9, Folder 202)
      - Lighting (Box 9, Folder 203)
      - Client meetings (Box 9, Folder 204)
      - Consultant coordination meeting (Box 9, Folder 205)
      - Site meetings (Box 9, Folder 206)
      - Specifications (Box 9, Folder 207)
      - Fees (Box 10, Folder 208)
      - Office schedules and project costing (Box 10, Folder 209)
      - Concept II report schematic design (Box 10, Folder 210)
      - Concept III report 35% submission (Box 10, Folder 211)
      - Pre-schematic report (Box 10, Folder 212)
    - Project images (Box 46, Folder 48)
    - Project drawings
      - Presentation and record drawings (Box 75)
      - Record drawings (Box 76)
    - Project sketches (Box 123, Folder 48-49)
  - Riverwalk, Chevron Land and Development Corporation (San Diego, CA) (91021), 1991-1992
    See Also: 89019
    - Project file (Box 10, Folder 213-219)
    - Project images (Box 46, Folder 49)
    - Project drawings (Box 77)
    - Project sketches (Box 123, Folder 50)
  - Celebration (Celebration, FL) (91023), 1987-2000
    See Also: 87033
    - Project file
      - Pre-design (Box 10, Folder 220)
      - Project notebooks (Box 10, Folder 221)
      - Client - Disney (Box 10, Folder 222)
      - Client - town (Box 10, Folder 223)
      - Client - town center, 1993 to 1995 (Box 10, Folder 224)
      - Client - town center, 1996 to 1997 (Box 11, Folder 225)
      - Fee, contract, and scope of services (Box 11, Folder 226)
      - Additional services (Box 11, Folder 227)
      - Billing (Box 11, Folder 228)
      - Precedents (Box 11, Folder 229)
      - Office schedules and responsibility matrices (Box 11, Folder 230)
      - Project statistics (Box 110, Folder 231)
      - Cost consultants, cost estimates (Box 11, Folder 232)
      - Authorities (permits, filings, and approvals) (Box 11, Folder 233)
      - Architect of record, 1993 to 1996 (Box 11, Folder 234-235)
      - Parking/traffic (Box 12, Folder 236)
      - Civil (Box 12, Folder 237)
      - Fire-life safety/accessibility (Box 12, Folder 238)
      - Landscape (Box 12, Folder 239)
      - Apartment plan consultants (Box 12, Folder 240)
      - Model makers (Box 12, Folder 241)
      - Graphics (Box 12, Folder 242)
      - Lighting (Box 12, Folder 243)
      - Acoustics (Box 12, Folder 244)
      - Residential design guidelines (Box 12, Folder 245)
      - Food service design (Box 12, Folder 246)
      - Cooper Robertson, 1992 to 1998 (Box 12, Folder 247-248)
      - Potential town architecs (Box 12, Folder 249)
      - Agenda and minutes (Box 12, Folder 250)
      - Client meetings, memos (Box 12, Folder 251)
      - Consultant coordination meetings (Box 12, Folder 252)
      - Site meetings (Box 12, Folder 253)
      - Progress photos (Box 12, Folder 254)
      - Slide shows (Box 13, Folder 255)
      - Team meetings (Box 13, Folder 256)
      - Quarterly meetings (Box 13, Folder 257)
      - Drawings (Box 13, Folder 258)
      - Town plans (Box 13, Folder 259)
      - Town housing types (Box 13, Folder 260)
      - Town center plans (Box 13, Folder 261)
      - Town center unit types (Box 13, Folder 262)
      - Town center elevations (Box 13, Folder 263)
      - Town center building plans (Box 13, Folder 264)
      - Recreation and amenity plans (Box 13, Folder 265)
      - Miscellaneous town drawings (Box 13, Folder 266)
      - Project manual - volumes 1 to 6 (Box 13, Folder 267-272)
      - Publicity (Box 13, Folder 273)
      - Project narrative (Box 13, Folder 274)
    - Project images
      - Slides, negative, prints - 1991 to 2000 (Box 46, Folder 50-54)
      - Slides, prints - 1994 to 2000 (Box 47, Folder 55-56)
    - Project drawings
      - Design development, 50% (Box 77)
      - Design development and schematic design, 100% (Box 78)
    - Project sketches (Box 124, Folder 51-59)
  - Residence in Starwood (Aspen, CO) (91024), 1991-1999
    - Project file
      - Program and briefing (Box 14, Folder 275)
      - Aspen - Pitkin Building Department (Box 14, Folder 276)
      - Starwood Home Owners Association (Box 14, Folder 277)
      - To client - 1991 to 1998 (Box 14, Folder 278-285)
      - From client (Box 14, Folder 286)
      - Authorities (permits, filings, and approvals) (Box 14, Folder 287)
      - Cost estimates (Box 14, Folder 288)
      - Structural (Box 14, Folder 289)
      - Mechanical - 1991 to 1998 (Box 14, Folder 290-293)
      - Electrical (Box 14, Folder 294)
      - Lighting (Box 14, Folder 295)
      - Landscaping (Box 14, Folder 296)
      - Surveyor and geotechnical engineer (Box 14, Folder 297)
      - Interior decorating (Box 15, Folder 298)
      - Fireplaces (Box 15, Folder 299)
      - Stereo system (Box 15, Folder 300)
      - Harware (Box 15, Folder 301)
      - Security system (Box 15, Folder 302)
      - Telephone system (Box 15, Folder 303)
      - Client meetings (Box 15, Folder 304)
      - Site meetings (Box 15, Folder 305)
      - Memos, clarifications, notes (Box 15, Folder 306)
      - Specifications - project manual, schedules (Box 15, Folder 307-308)
      - Bids and quotations (Box 15, Folder 309)
      - Nominated suppliers and sub-contractors (Box 15, Folder 310)
      - To contractor - 1991 to 1993 (Box 15, Folder 311)
      - To contractor - 1994 to 1999 (Box 16, Folder 312-314)
      - From contractor (Box 16, Folder 315)
      - Field reports, schedules, and progress reports (Box 16, Folder 316)
      - Punch list (Box 16, Folder 317)
      - As-built drawings and manuals (Box 16, Folder 318)
      - Fees (Box 16, Folder 319)
      - Office schedules and project costing (Box 16, Folder 320)
      - Photographing and publicity (Box 16, Folder 321)
      - Telephone log (Box 16, Folder 322)
    - Project images (Box 47, Folder 57-59)
    - Project drawings
      - Design, presentation, and monograph (Box 79)
      - Working drawings - building department and construction (Box 80)
      - Working drawings - construction (Box 81)
      - Working drawings - construction, interior design, stone details (Box 82)
      - Small-scale design drawings (Box 125, Folder 64)
    - Project sketches (Box 125, Folder 60-63)
  - Agins House (Tiburon, CA) (91025), 1991
    - Project file (Box 17, Folder 323)
    - Project images (Box 47, Folder 60)
  - Amster Residence (Water Mill, NY) (91028), 1991
    See Also: 84249
    - Project file (Box 17, Folder 324)
    - Project images (Box 47, Folder 61)
    - Project sketches (Box 125, Folder 65)
  - Feature Animation Building, The Walt Disney Company (Burbank, CA) (91029), 1991-1994
    - Project file
      - Pre-design (Box 17, Folder 325)
      - To client - 1991 to 1994 (Box 17, Folder 326-329)
      - From client (Box 17, Folder 330)
      - Authorities (permits, filings, and approvals) (Box 17, Folder 331)
      - Cost consultants (Box 17, Folder 332)
      - Programming (Box 17, Folder 333)
      - Structural (Box 17, Folder 334)
      - Mechanical, electrical, and plumbing (Box 17, Folder 335)
      - Civil (Box 17, Folder 336)
      - Landscape (Box 17, Folder 337)
      - Soil engineer (Box 17, Folder 338)
      - Lighting (Box 17, Folder 339)
      - Kitchen (Box 17, Folder 340)
      - Acoustic (Box 17, Folder 341)
      - Elevator (Box 17, Folder 342)
      - Associate architect - 1992 to 1994 (Box 17, Folder 343-345)
      - Interiors (Box 17, Folder 346)
      - Acoustic (Box 18, Folder 347)
      - Client meetings (Box 18, Folder 348)
      - Consultant coordination meetings (Box 18, Folder 349)
      - Site meetings (Box 18, Folder 350)
      - Specifications (Box 18, Folder 351)
      - Bids and quotations (Box 18, Folder 352)
      - To and from contractor (Box 18, Folder 353-354)
      - Request for information (RFI) (Box 18, Folder 355)
      - Change orders (Box 18, Folder 356)
      - As-built drawings (Box 18, Folder 357)
      - Fees (Box 18, Folder 358)
      - Office schedules and project costing (Box 18, Folder 359)
      - Project book (Box 18, Folder 360)
    - Project images (Box 48, Folder 62-66)
    - Project drawings
      - Design, monograph, presentation, schematics, working drawings (Box 83)
      - Working drawings - design development and tenant interiors (Box 84)
      - Small-scale presentation drawings (Box 125, Folder 67)
    - Project sketches (Box 125, Folder 66)
  - Brooks School Library (North Andover, MA) (91030), 1991-1994
    - Project images (Box 48, Folder 67)
    - Project drawings
      - Mylar originals, including presentation (Box 85)
      - Small-scale design drawings (Box 126, Folder 69)
    - Project sketches (Box 126, Folder 68)
  - Lighting for Baldinger (91031)
    - Project file (Box 18, Folder 361-367)
    - Project images (Box 48, Folder 68)
    - Project drawings, small-scale design (Box 18, Folder 365-366)
    - Project sketches (Box 126, Folder 70)
  - Bachrach House (Decatur, IL) (91032), 1991-1994
    - Project file (Box 18, Folder 368-383)
    - Project images (Box 48, Folder 69)
    - Project drawings
      - Presentation drawings (Box 85)
      - Working drawings (Box 86)
    - Project sketches (Box 126, Folder 71)
  - Battery Place Residential Area (New York, NY) (91035), 1991
    - Project file (Box 18, Folder 384-390)
    - Project images (Box 48, Folder 70)
    - Project drawings and sketches (Box 126, Folder 72-73)
  - Bozzi House Landscape (East Hampton, NY) (91036), 1991-1992
    See Also: 80128, 99028, A03028
    - Project images (Box 48, Folder 71)
    - Project sketches (Box 126, Folder 74)
  - Colgate Darden School of Business, University of Virginia (Charlottesville, VA) (92001), 1992-1996
    - Project file
      - Pre-design (Box 19, Folder 391)
      - To client - 1992 to 1995 (Box 19, Folder 392-396)
      - From client - 1992 to 1996 (Box 19, Folder 397-402)
      - Authorities (permits, filings, and approvals) (Box 19, Folder 403)
      - Cost consultants - 1992 to 1994 (Box 19, Folder 404-405)
      - Associated architect - 1993-1996 (Box 19, Folder 406-408)
      - Structural (Box 19, Folder 409)
      - Mechanical, electrical, and plumbing (Box 19, Folder 410)
      - Civil (Box 19, Folder 411)
      - Landscape - 1992 to 1995 (Box 20, Folder 412-414)
      - Landscape, gardens (Box 20, Folder 415)
      - Lighting (Box 20, Folder 416)
      - Kitchen (Box 20, Folder 417)
      - Graphic designer (Box 20, Folder 418)
      - Acoustics/AV (Box 20, Folder 419)
      - Code consultant (Box 20, Folder 420)
      - Client meetings (Box 20, Folder 421)
      - Consultant coordination meetings (Box 20, Folder 422)
      - Specifications (Box 20, Folder 423-425)
      - Specifications (Box 21, Folder 426-428)
      - To and from construction manager/contractor (Box 21, Folder 429-430)
      - Fees (Box 21, Folder 431)
      - Office schedules and drawing reference lists (Box 21, Folder 432)
      - Publicity (Box 21, Folder 433)
      - GB (Box 21, Folder 434-436)
      - Interiors (Box 21, Folder 437)
    - Project images (Box 48, Folder 72-77)
    - Project drawings
      - Design drawings and details, Commons Building (Box 87)
      - Details, monograph, and presentation (Box 88)
      - Presentation drawings (Box 89)
      - Presentation and working (Box 90)
      - Working drawings (Box 91)
      - Working drawings, Sponsor's Hall (Box 92)
      - Small-scale presentation drawings (Box 127, Folder 77)
    - Project sketches (Box 127, Folder 75-76)
  - Furniture for Lane (92002), 1992-1993
    No designs produced.
    - Project images (Box 48, Folder 78)
    - Project sketches (Box 127, Folder 78-80)
  - Red Oaks (Cohasset, MA) (92004), 1992-1996
    - Project file (Box 22, Folder 438-460)
    - Project images (Box 49, Folder 79-81)
    - Project drawings
      - Presentation and working (Box 92)
      - Working drawings (Box 93)
      - Small drawings (Box 22, Folder 461)
    - Project sketches (Box 127, Folder 81)
  - Nanki-Shirahama Golf Clubhouse (Wakayama Prefecture, Japan) (92006), 1992
    - Project file (Box 22, Folder 462-467)
    - Project images (Box 49, Folder 82)
    - Project drawings (Box 94)
    - Project sketches (Box 127, Folder 82)
  - Phelan-Griff Residence (Summit, NJ) (92007), 1992
    - Project file (Box 23, Folder 468)
    - Project images (Box 49, Folder 83)
    - Project drawings (Box 94)
    - Project sketches (Box 127, Folder 83)
  - Gap Inc. Offices at Two Folsom Street (San Francisco, CA) (92008), 1992-2001
    - Project file
      - Pre-design (Box 23, Folder 469)
      - To client - 1992 to 2001 (Box 23, Folder 470-474)
      - From client - 1992 to 2001 (Box 23, Folder 475-478)
      - Authorities (permits, filings, and approvals) (Box 23, Folder 479)
      - Associate architect, 1997 to 1998 (Box 23, Folder 480-482)
      - Associate architect, 1999 to 2001 (Box 24, Folder 483-485)
      - Landscape (Box 24, Folder 486)
      - Lighting (Box 24, Folder 487)
      - Minutes (Box 24, Folder 488)
      - Consultant coordination meetings (Box 24, Folder 489)
      - Site meetings (Box 24, Folder 490)
      - Specifications (Box 24, Folder 491)
      - Suppliers and sub-contractors (Box 24, Folder 492)
      - To and from contractor (Box 24, Folder 493-497)
      - Field reports (Box 24, Folder 498)
      - Office schedules (Box 25, Folder 499)
      - Publicity (Box 25, Folder 500)
      - Fees (Box 25, Folder 501)
      - Competition (Box 25, Folder 502)
      - Presentation booklets (Box 25, Folder 503)
    - Project images (Box 49, Folder 84-90)
    - Project drawings
      - Presentation drawings - mylar originals and sepia prints (Box 94)
      - Presentation drawings - vellum originals and prints (Box 95)
    - Project sketches (Box 128, Folder 84-85)
  - Ferrin Kitchen Renovation (92009), 1992
    - Project file (Box 25, Folder 504)
    - Project images (Box 50, Folder 91)
    - Project drawings (Box 95)
  - Residence at Kings Point (Kings Point, NY) (92010), 1992-1999
    - Project file
      - Pre-design (Box 25, Folder 505)
      - Existing conditions (Box 25, Folder 506)
      - To and from client (Box 25, Folder 507-508)
      - Authorities (permits, filings, and approvals) - 1992 to 1996 (Box 25, Folder 509-510)
      - Consultants (Box 25, Folder 511)
      - Structural (Box 25, Folder 512)
      - Mechanical, electrical, and plumbing (Box 25, Folder 513)
      - Electrical (Box 26, Folder 514)
      - Plumbing (Box 26, Folder 515)
      - HVAC, 1995 to 1999 (Box 26, Folder 516-518)
      - To and from contractor (Box 26, Folder 519-522)
      - Field reports - 1994 to 1997 (Box 26, Folder 523-524)
      - Change orders/bulletins (Box 26, Folder 525)
      - Final completion (Box 26, Folder 526)
      - As-built drawings and manuals (Box 26, Folder 527)
      - Office schedules and project costing (Box 26, Folder 528)
      - Soil engineers (Box 27, Folder 529)
      - Surveyor (Box 27, Folder 530)
      - Landscape, 1992 to 1998 (Box 27, Folder 531-534)
      - Interior design (Box 27, Folder 535)
      - LIghting (Box 27, Folder 536)
      - Minutes (Box 27, Folder 537)
      - Project manual (Box 27, Folder 538-539)
      - Doors and windows (Box 27, Folder 540)
      - Stone (Box 27, Folder 541)
      - Hardware (Box 27, Folder 542)
      - Greenhouse (Box 28, Folder 543)
      - Poolhouse (Box 28, Folder 544)
    - Project images (Box 50, Folder 92-95)
    - Project drawings
      - Presentation drawings (Box 95)
      - Presentation and working (Box 96)
      - Working drawings (Box 97)
      - Working drawings (Box 98)
      - Working drawings (Box 99)
      - Small drawings - ESKs (Box 28, Folder 545)
    - Project sketches (Box 128, Folder 86-88)
  - Robert A. M. Stern Architects Office: Building Lobby (New York, NY) (92011), 1992
    See Also: 85025, 90009, 91013
    - Project file (Box 28, Folder 546-554)
    - Project images (Box 50, Folder 96)
    - Project drawings
      - Working drawings (Box 100)
      - Small drawings (Box 28, Folder 555)
  - Town Square -- Upper Saddle River (Saddle River, NJ) (92012), 1992
    - Project file (Box 28, Folder 556)
    - Project images (Box 50, Folder 97)
    - Project sketches (Box 129, Folder 89)
  - Aspen Highlands (Aspen, CO) (92013), 1992-1996
    This is an unbuilt project. This project was continued and eventually realized under RAMSA project number 96027.
    - Project file
      - Pre-design (Box 28, Folder 557)
      - To and from client (Box 28, Folder 558-560)
      - Authorities (permits, filings, and approvals) (Box 28, Folder 561)
      - Cost consultants (Box 29, Folder 562)
      - Master planning - Davis Horn (Box 29, Folder 563)
      - Associate architects (Box 29, Folder 564)
      - Mountain planners (Box 29, Folder 565)
      - Associate landscape architect (Box 29, Folder 566)
      - Civil/Traffic engineer (Box 29, Folder 567-568)
      - Energy Consultants (Box 29, Folder 569)
      - Lighting (Box 29, Folder 570)
      - Project attorney (Box 29, Folder 571)
      - Structural (Box 29, Folder 572)
      - Client meetings (Box 29, Folder 573)
      - Consultant coordination meetings (Box 29, Folder 574)
      - Specifications (Box 29, Folder 575)
      - Fees (Box 29, Folder 576)
      - Office schedules and project costing (Box 29, Folder 577)
      - Publicity (Box 29, Folder 578-579)
    - Project images (Box 50, Folder 98-99)
    - Project drawings
      - Design drawings, presentation drawings (Box 100)
      - Design drawings, presentation drawings, and general submission (Box 101)
    - Project sketches (Box 129, Folder 90-92)
  - William Gates Computer Science Building, Stanford University (Palo Alto, CA) (92014), 1992-1996
    See Also: 94021
    - Project file
      - Pre-design (Box 30, Folder 580)
      - To client - 1992 to 1996 (Box 30, Folder 581-585)
      - From client - 1992 to 1996 (Box 30, Folder 586-590)
      - Authorities (permits, filings, and approvals) (Box 30, Folder 591)
      - Cost consultants (Box 30, Folder 592)
      - Associated architect, 1992 to 1996 (Box 31, Folder 593-597)
      - Structural (Box 31, Folder 598)
      - Mechanical, electrical, and plumbing - 1992 to 1996 (Box 31, Folder 599-601)
      - Civil (Box 31, Folder 602)
      - Landscape (Box 31, Folder 603)
      - Soils engineer (Box 32, Folder 604)
      - Lighting (Box 32, Folder 605)
      - Acoustic (Box 32, Folder 606)
      - Elevator consultant (Box 32, Folder 607)
      - Audio Visual (Box 32, Folder 608)
      - CDC stone consultant (Box 32, Folder 609)
      - Interior designer (Box 32, Folder 610)
      - Minutes (Box 32, Folder 611)
      - Client meetings (Box 32, Folder 612)
      - Consultant coordination meetings (Box 32, Folder 613)
      - Site meetings (Box 32, Folder 614)
      - Specifications (Box 32, Folder 615)
      - To and from construction manager/contractor (Box 32, Folder 616-617)
      - Fees - additional services and base contract (Box 32, Folder 618-619)
      - Office schedules and project costing (Box 32, Folder 620)
      - Publicity (Box 32, Folder 621)
    - Project images (Box 50, Folder 100-101)
    - Project drawings
      - Small drawings (Box 32, Folder 622)
      - Monograph drawings (Box 101)
      - Presentation and record set - design development (Box 102)
      - Record set - design development and schematic design (Box 103)
      - Small-scale design and presentation drawings (Box 129, Folder 96)
    - Project sketches (Box 129, Folder 93-95)
  - Residence at Skimhampton (East Hampton, NY) (92016), 1992-1993
    - Project file (Box 33, Folder 623-637)
    - Project images (Box 50, Folder 102)
    - Project drawings (Box 103)
    - Project sketches (Box 130, Folder 97)
  - Dabbah Residence (Geneva, Switzerland) (92017), 1992
    This is an unbuilt project. It appears that a house based on the initial drawings was built, by a local architect, though it was demolished sometime in the 2000s.
    - Project file (Box 33, Folder 638)
    - Project images (Box 50, Folder 103)
  - St. Paul's School Dormitory (Concord, NH) (92018), 1992
    - Project file (Box 33, Folder 639)
    - Project drawings (Box 103)
    - Project sketches (Box 130, Folder 98)
  - BRH Dialysis TI at Columbus Medical Office Building (Columbus, IN) (92019), project file, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 640)
    See Also: 91002
  - Telluride House (Telluride, CO) (92020), 1992
    - Project file (Box 33, Folder 641-645)
    - Project images (Box 51, Folder 104)
    - Project drawings (Box 104)
      - Mylar originals, presentation drawings (Box 104)
      - Small-scale presentation drawings (Box 130, Folder 101)
    - Project sketches (Box 130, Folder 99-100)
  - Residence in Beverly Park (Beverly Park, CA) (92021), 1992-1994
    See Also: 87027, 89032, 95044, A10031
    - Project file (Box 33, Folder 646-662)
    - Project images (Box 51, Folder 105)
    - Project drawings
      - Design and presentation (Box 104)
      - Presentation and record (Box 105)
      - Record drawings (Box 106)
      - Small-scale presentation drawings (Box 130, Folder 103)
    - Project sketches (Box 130, Folder 102)
  - Concept Plan for Georgetown's Future (Washington, D.C.) (92022), 1992-1995
    See Also: 92022.08
    - Project file (Box 34, Folder 663-677)
    - Project images (Box 51, Folder 106)
    - Project drawings
      - Presentation drawings (Box 107)
      - Small-scale presentation drawings (Box 131, Folder 107)
    - Project sketches (Box 130, Folder 104-106)
  - Mount Vernon College Concept Plan (Washington, D.C.) (92022.08), 1993-1994
    See Also: 92022
    - Project file (Box 34, Folder 678-684)
    - Project images (Box 51, Folder 107)
    - Project drawings
      - Presentation, mylar originals (Box 107)
      - Presentation, sepia mylar prints (Box 108)
  - M. Griffin Property (Los Angeles, CA) (92023), 1992
    - Project file (Box 34, Folder 685)
    - Project images (Box 51, Folder 108)
  - Additions to Points of View - Main House (Mount Desert Island, ME) (92024), 1992-1993
    See Also: 75062, 90027, 92024.01
    - Project file (Box 35, Folder 686-699)
    - Project images (Box 51, Folder 109)
    - Project drawings (Box 108)
    - Project sketches (Box 131, Folder 108)
  - Additions to Points of View - Squash House (Mount Desert Island, ME) (92024.01), 1992-1993
    See Also: 75062, 90027, 92024